Guide to the William Darlington Papers 1800-1863 MS 1165
New-York Historical Society
- Series I. Correspondence, 1800-1863
  - Fell, Eliza (Volume 9, Item 384-386, 388-408, 410-421, 453-465)
  - Fell, Sarah Ann (Volume 9, Item 598)
  - Gault, Agnus H.Y. (Volume 9, Item 543)
  - Gray, Jane L. (Volume 9, Item 134)
  - Griffin, William Preston (Volume 9, Item 262)
  - Hanford, Mary A.C. (Volume 9, Item 515-518, 519-522, 523-526, 527-528)
  - Hanna, Annette (Volume 9, Item 559-560)
  - Harris, Sarah Coates (Volume 9, Item 552-553, 554-555, 587-588)
  - Hemenway, Abby Maria (Volume 9, Item 595-596)
  - Horn, Michael (Volume 9, Item 145, 146)
  - Jaffrey, George (Volume 9, Item 266)
  - Jaffrey, Marie Harriette (Volume 9, Item 258/259, 260/261, 264/265, 267-290)
  - James, Isabella (Volume 9, Item 532A/533, 534/535)
  - Levengord, Pos. (Volume 9, Item 246)
  - Loss, Virginia (Volume 9, Item 561)
  - Macalester, Lily L. (Volume 9, Item 538/539, 547/548, 550/551)
  - McLeod, Sophie de V. (Volume 9, Item 608)
  - Missing (Volume 9, Item 203, 243, 331-339, 510)
  - Morris, Andrew Anna (Volume 9, Item 422, 606)
  - Morris, Elizabeth C. (Volume 9, Item 1/2-106/107, 109-133, 135/136-143/144, 147/148-202, 204/205-242, 244/245, 247/248-257)
  - Morrison, Anne D. (Volume 9, Item 602A/603)
  - Music (Soiree Musicale) (Volume 9, Item 540)
  - Pamphlets - Lists (Volume 9, Item 108)
  - Pearce, Martha E. (Volume 9, Item 572)
  - Phelps, A. Maria Lincoln (Volume 9, Item 511/512, 529, 580-582)
  - Preston, Ann, Dr. (Volume 9, Item 570/571, 601/602, 610/611)
  - Richardson, H.W. (Volume 9, Item 573/574)
  - Royall, Anne (Volume 9, Item 530)
  - Sharpless, Lydia (Volume 9, Item 575, 576-578/579)
  - Smith, Elizabeth P. (Volume 9, Item 387, 426/427-451/452, 466/467-476)
  - Thomas, Mary B. (Volume 9, Item 423)
  - Vaughan, Eliza (Volume 9, Item 424/425)
  - Woodward, A.Y. (Volume 9, Item 604/605)
  - Wright, E.C. (Volume 9, Item 589/590)
  - Adams Express Company (Volume 10, Item 309)
  - Allen, F.A. (Volume 10, Item 202, 274)
  - Allibone, S. Austin (Volume 10, Item 20, 322, 324/330)
  - Atkins, Layton Y. (Volume 10, Item 109)
  - Bache, A.D. (Volume 10, Item 173)
  - Bacon, J. Barnitz (Volume 10, Item 73)
  - Baird, Spencer F. (Volume 10, Item 86, 130)
  - Balch, Lewis P.W. (Volume 10, Item 92, 94)
  - Barnard, Henry (Volume 10, Item 316, 320)
  - Barnard, Vincent (Volume 10, Item 183, 272, 292)
  - Bell, Thomas S. (Volume 10, Item 33, 37, 40)
  - Benson, Alexander (Volume 10, Item 295)
  - Biddle, J.B. (Volume 10, Item 74)
  - Blackie, George S. (Volume 10, Item 63, 72, 137, 141, 237)
  - Blakiston & Lindsay (Volume 10, Item 54, 55)
  - Blodget, Lorin (Volume 10, Item 30)
  - Botanists, Moravian (Volume 10, Item 104-107)
  - Bowen, John S. (Volume 10, Item 38/39)
  - Bradley, John H. (Volume 10, Item 307)
  - Brickenstein, Herman (Volume 10, Item 100/101)
  - Caldwell, George C. (Volume 10, Item 56, 57)
  - Canby, William M. (Volume 10, Item 294)
  - Carey, H.C. (Volume 10, Item 310, 312)
  - Carson, J. (Volume 10, Item 136)
  - Childs, George W. (Volume 10, Item 236A)
  - Churchman, C. (Volume 10, Item 90, 91)
  - Clemson, Thomas G. (Volume 10, Item 243)
  - Conarroe, George M. (Volume 10, Item 21, 22, 24, 25, 26, 27, 36, 118, 125, 273, 275)
  - Cook, Charles (Volume 10, Item 287/288)
  - Cope, Edward D. (Volume 10, Item 186)
  - Curtis, Moses A., Rev. (Volume 10, Item 153/154, 254/255, 250/251)
  - Cutter, Calvin, Dr. (Volume 10, Item 200)
  - Darlington, Edward C. (Volume 10, Item 75, 79, 152, 158A)
  - Darlington, Henry T. (Volume 10, Item 89)
  - Darlington, Jared (Volume 10, Item 298)
  - Darlington, John Lacey (Volume 10, Item 299)
  - Darlington, Samuel S. (Volume 10, Item 325)
  - Darlington, William (Volume 10, Item 42, 175)
  - Darlington, William B. (Volume 10, Item 167)
  - Davis, John (Volume 10, Item 303)
  - Davis, W.W.H. (Volume 10, Item 121, 228, 249, 256)
  - Dean, John Ward (Volume 10, Item 65/66, 123/124, 144/145, 165, 166, 197, 264, 266)
  - DeHaas, W., Dr. (Volume 10, Item 139, 140)
  - Derby & Jackson (Volume 10, Item 41)
  - Devereux & Company (Volume 10, Item 161)
  - Draper, Lyman C. (Volume 10, Item 219, 232/235, 293)
  - Duane, William (Volume 10, Item 170)
  - Ducachet, H.W., Rev. (Volume 10, Item 159)
  - Durand, E. (Volume 10, Item 112, 179)
  - Durrie, D.S. (Volume 10, Item 70)
  - Elliott, Charles J. (Volume 10, Item 215)
  - Elwyn, Alfred Langdon (Volume 10, Item 233/234)
  - Evans, Alexander (Volume 10, Item 44)
  - Everett, Edward (Volume 10, Item 78)
  - Fergus, Thomas H. (Volume 10, Item 96)
  - Feuchtwanger, Lewis (Volume 10, Item 28)
  - Finney, William, Rev. (Volume 10, Item 280/281)
  - Flowers, William P. (Volume 10, Item 132/133)
  - Givin, James (Volume 10, Item 151)
  - Graham, J.D. (Volume 10, Item 168/169, 209/210, 248, 262)
  - Gray, Asa, Dr. (Volume 10, Item 317, 327/328, 329)
  - Gross, S.D. (Volume 10, Item 253)
  - Hall, James (Volume 10, Item 71)
  - Hazard, Samuel (Volume 10, Item 35, 129, 304)
  - Henry, Joseph (Volume 10, Item 108)
  - Hickman, John (Volume 10, Item 51, 127, 128, 201)
  - Historical Society of Iowa (Volume 10, Item 172/176, 184/185)
  - Historical Society of Pennsylvania (Volume 10, Item 300)
  - Horticultural Society of Pennsylvania (Volume 10, Item 47)
  - Hough, A.L. (Volume 10, Item 180)
  - Independent Republican Clipping (Volume 10, Item 192)
  - Irvine, William A. (Volume 10, Item 198/199, 216/218, 308)
  - Irvingiana (Volume 10, Item 213)
  - Ivision (of Ivision & Phinney) (Volume 10, Item 34)
  - J.B. Lippincott & Company (Volume 10, Item 126)
  - James, Thomas P. (Volume 10, Item 48/51, 49/50)
  - Johnson, Professor - Yale College (Volume 10, Item 60/61)
  - Jordan, John, Jr. (Volume 10, Item 95)
  - Kille, Jane (Volume 10, Item 23)
  - Knapp, Clark (Volume 10, Item 246/247)
  - Lanman, Charles (Volume 10, Item 134, 135, 148-150)
  - Lee, L. Collins (Volume 10, Item 45/46, 76, 77, 80/81, 82-83)
  - Lewis, Joseph J. (Volume 10, Item 242)
  - Lewis, Samuel (Volume 10, Item 208/211)
  - Lossing, Benson J. (Volume 10, Item 187-190, 194/195, 196, 206/207, 217, 220-225, 238/239)
  - Maps (Folio Atlas of Climatological Maps) (Volume 10, Item 31)
  - McEuen, Thomas, Dr. (Volume 10, Item 258/259, 270/271, 278)
  - M'Cullough, William (Volume 10, Item 313/314)
  - Meehan, Thomas (Volume 10, Item 68/69, 110, 181/182)
  - Michener, Ezra, Dr. (Volume 10, Item 40561)
  - Missing (Volume 10, Item 193)
  - Montgomery, William (Volume 10, Item 289/290)
  - Moore, Augustus O. (Volume 10, Item 52/53, 62, 64)
  - Mount Vernon Fund-Aid (Volume 10, Item 160)
  - New England Historic-Genealogical Society, 1860 (Volume 10, Item 265)
  - Newton, William (Volume 10, Item 245)
  - Niles, Hezekiah (Volume 10, Item 323)
  - Obituary Notices (Volume 10, Item 240/241)
  - Palmer, W.R. (Volume 10, Item 231)
  - Parry, John S. (Volume 10, Item 252, 271A)
  - Pearce, George W. (Volume 10, Item 226/227, 230)
  - Penington, Jno & Son (Volume 10, Item 32, 155)
  - Pennsylvania Horticultural Society (Volume 10, Item 47)
  - Perkins, P.L. (Volume 10, Item 67)
  - Phelps, J.W., Capt. (Volume 10, Item 87/88, 163/164, 267/268, 268A, 269)
  - Philadelphians, Lives of Eminent (Volume 10, Item 305/306)
  - Phinney (of Ivision & Phinney) (Volume 10, Item 34)
  - Pugh, Evan (Volume 10, Item 58/59)
  - Randall, Henry S. (Volume 10, Item 114-117, 119/120)
  - Read, Zachary, Dr. (Volume 10, Item 174, 178)
  - Reinke, C.L. (Volume 10, Item 98)
  - Rice, Owen, Jr. (Volume 10, Item 142)
  - Richardson, Charles B. (& Company) (Volume 10, Item 212, 214, 311/315, 321/331, 326)
  - Ripley, George (Volume 10, Item 279A)
  - Saunders, William (Volume 10, Item 131, 138)
  - Short, C.W. (Volume 10, Item 156/157, 162)
  - Smith, Thomas (Volume 10, Item 296/297)
  - Spanger, A.M. (Volume 10, Item 263)
  - Steele, John D. (Volume 10, Item 203-205)
  - Stoddard, J.F. (Volume 10, Item 177, 192)
  - Swayne, W. Marshall (Volume 10, Item 229)
  - Tatnall, Edward, Jr. (Volume 10, Item 97, 279/277)
  - Taylor, Franklin (Volume 10, Item 197A)
  - Tefft, J.K. (Volume 10, Item 171)
  - The Greenwood Literary Society (Volume 10, Item 113)
  - Thomas, David (Volume 10, Item 122, 145A)
  - Thurber, George (Volume 10, Item 70A, 146/147)
  - Veech, James (Volume 10, Item 260/261)
  - Walter, Thomas N. (Volume 10, Item 84/85)
  - Ward, Townsend (Pennsylvania Historical Society) (Volume 10, Item 93, 111, 191, 257, 291, 301, 302, 318/319)
  - Wilson, William C. (Volume 10, Item 282-286)
  - Wolle, Jacob (Volume 10, Item 99)
  - Woodward, Ashbel (Volume 10, Item 276/277)
  - Wyers, William F. (Volume 10, Item 29, 43, 158, 236)
- Series II. Diaries and Scrapbooks, 1804-1863, undated
  - The Tullian Miscellany; or an Historical Account of the Philadelphia Tullian Society, 1804 (Box BV Darlington 3)
  - Ship Bengal, Capt. Donnaldson, from Calcutta towards Philadelphia, 1807 (Box BV Darlington 1)
  - A Speculative Journey up the Susquehanna, 1810 (Box BV Darlington 1)
  - Revolutionary Scraps, circa 1814-1861 (Box BV Darlington 1)
  - [Diary], circa 1815-1821 (Box BV Darlington 1)
  - Diary of Transactions, Incidents, Observations & Reflections, 1822 (Box BV Darlington 3)
  - [Scrapbook], circa 1827-1863 (Box BV Darlington 2)
  - Minutes of the State Road Commissioners, 1830 (Box BV Darlington 1)
  - Incidents and Reminiscences connected with the Personal Career of William Darlington, 1858 (Box BV Darlington 2)
  - A Collection of Songs; Patriotic, Political, Social, Amatory, and Burlesque, or Sportive. (Box BV Darlington 3)